--- 1 ---
 The Documentation Cutoff is 07-Oct-2022 17:00.
Booking Confirmation
Booking Number 2LIM014486
 Agreement No(s). Shipper Reference Edi Reference No. Proposed BL No.
EURC2000069
200795501
Created by Created on Phone E-Mail
Customer Booking Desk 15-AUG-2022 16:16
LIM-ExportCS@hamburgsud.com
 Merchant is obliged to provide all documents necessary for this shipment to the Carrier until the applicable documentation cut-off date and time 07-Oct-2022 17:00. If this cut-off date and time is not met, the Carrier reserves the right to transfer the shipment to the next available vessel, all additional costs being for the account of the Merchant.
All the local charges occurring at Peru to be paid by the merchants duly identified in the BL. These local charges are published on the website https://agenciacolumbus.com/servicios/tarifario/ together with a detailed description. Merchants acknowledge and accept these local charges when contracting our services, other charges might be applicable.
 Booking Party
Contact Phone E-Mail Fax
Shipper
Origin Destination
Ves/Voy/Dir
Transport Plan
CIA. INTERNACIONAL DEL CAFE S.A.C. (COINCA)
CARRETERA OLMOS CORRAL QUEMADO KM 182
BAYOVAR PERU
MS AMPARO PEREYRA
511 536 8900 AMPARO.PEREYRA@NKG.COFFEE 511 537 0503
CIA. INTERNACIONAL DEL CAFE S.A.C. (COINCA)
BAYOVAR, PE
CALLAO, PE (PECLL) (PORT)
MONTREAL, QC, CA (CAMTR) (INLAND TERMINAL)
POLAR COSTA RICA 239 N
Booking Agreement Party
ICL INTL COMMODITY LOGISTIK GMBH AM SANDTORPARK 4
20457 HAMBURG
GERMANY
 Cargo Cut-Off
Estimated cargo availability at destination
06-OCT-2022 23:00 30-OCT-2022 13:30
 From / Planned Facility
 To / Planned Facility
 Mode
 Estimated Departure
 Estimated Arrival
 CALLAO, PE (PECLL) APM TERMINALS CALLAO
 BALBOA, PA (PABLB)
PPC CONTAINER TERMINAL BALBOA
 POLAR COSTA RICA 239 N LINER, ATACAMA
 08-OCT-2022 15:30
 13-OCT-2022 01:00
 BALBOA, PA (PABLB)
PPC CONTAINER TERMINAL BALBOA
 MANZANILLO, PA (PAMIT) MANZANILLO INTERNATIONAL TERMINAL (MIT)
 MAERSK BULAN 239 N LINER, CLX
 14-OCT-2022 14:30
 15-OCT-2022 19:00
 MANZANILLO, PA (PAMIT) MANZANILLO INTERNATIONAL TERMINAL (MIT)
 NEW YORK, NY, US (USNYC) APM TERMINALS ELIZABETH
 POLAR PERU 242 N
LINER, AGAS
 20-OCT-2022 05:00
 27-OCT-2022 07:00
 NEW YORK, NY, US (USNYC) APM TERMINALS ELIZABETH
 MONTREAL, QC, CA (CAMTR) CN MONTREAL RAMP
 RAIL
 28-OCT-2022 19:30
 30-OCT-2022 13:30
 Products
 Prod. ID
 Commodity
 Ship. Type
 Cargo Type
 00445
 COFFEE:(GREEN)-BAGS
 FCL
 GENERAL
 EQU
 Gross Cargo Weight/EQU
 Equipment Condition
 20GP
 20707 kg
   Qty
5
  HAMBURG SUED A/S
ESPLANADEN 50, 1263, COPENHAGEN, DENMARK -
Page 1 of 3
--- 1 ---
--- 2 ---
 Empty Equipment Pickup
Facility Details APMT INLAND SERVICES CALLAO NESTOR GAMBETA KM 14.5 S/N
CALLAO PERU
Full Equipment Delivery
Customer References
Please deliver the cargo to:
APM TERMINALS CALLAO
AVENIDA CONTRALMIRANTE RAYGADA 111 CALLAO
PERU
0051 1 2008800
Cargo Cut-Off:
06-OCT-2022 23:00
Booking Number 2LIM014486
  Container No.
 Prod. Item ID
 Facility
 EQU
 Pick Up Date/Time
 Empty Release Expiry
 MRKU7141977
 1
 APMT INLAND SERVICES CALLAO
 20GP
 29-SEP-2022 08:00
 10-OCT-2022 04:59
 MRKU8713906
 1
 APMT INLAND SERVICES CALLAO
 20GP
 29-SEP-2022 08:00
 10-OCT-2022 04:59
 MRKU8421150
 1
 APMT INLAND SERVICES CALLAO
 20GP
 29-SEP-2022 08:00
 10-OCT-2022 04:59
 SUDU7865915
 1
 APMT INLAND SERVICES CALLAO
 20GP
 29-SEP-2022 08:00
 10-OCT-2022 04:59
 TCKU1112095
 1
 APMT INLAND SERVICES CALLAO
 20GP
 29-SEP-2022 08:00
 10-OCT-2022 04:59
 Purchase Order No.: NI-2284093 / P43881 Shippers Reference No.: NI-2284093 / P43881
For pick-up and return of Containers please always use the appropriate Booking Number.
 Stowage of containers on vessels is subject to carrier's sole discretion (see clause 6. Hamburg Sud or Alianca Bill of Lading or Sea Waybill terms and conditions). Unless expressly agreed in writing the carrier does not undertake to accept any particular request, instruction or condition including, but not limited to, special stowage requirements.
The conditions of our Bills of Lading and Sea Waybills contain limitations of liability which deviate from German statute law.
Please note that Empty export containers are subject to an export detention.
Free time for Standard containers (incl. HC): 10 running days.
Free time for Special containers and Reefer containers (incl. NOR): 7 running days.
Free days start counting as from Gate-out Empty and end with Gate-in Full Export at port of loading.
Charges (subject to local IGV) to be paid by the Shipper and Merchant after free time:
Standard container(s) as from day 11 until day 15: USD 100/20' and USD 120/40' per day (sshinc). Standard container(s) as from day 16 on: USD 120/20' and USD 140/40' per day (sshinc).
Special container(s) as from day 8 until day 12: USD 130/20' and USD 130/40' per day (sshinc). Special container(s) as from day 13 on: USD 180/20' and USD 180/40' per day (sshinc).
Reefer container(s) as from day 8 until day 12: USD 180/20' and USD 180/40' per day (sshinc). Reefer container(s) as from day 13 on: USD 200/20' and USD 200/40' per day (sshinc).
NOR container(s) as from day 8 until day 12: USD 100/20' and USD 100/40' per day (sshinc). NOR container(s) as from day 13 on: USD 200/20' and USD 200/40' per day (sshinc).
Booking confirmation subject that cargo is non prescribed (non flag bound).
Dangerous Goods Procedure – in the interest of safety of our crew, our vessels, the environment, and our customers ́ cargo, Hamburg Sud will charge a Dangerous Goods Misdeclaration Fee of USD 5,000 per booking. The fee will be applicable if cargo containing hazardous commodities is not completely and correctly declared, prior to handing the cargo over into Hamburg Sud ́s custody. Any additional costs resulting from taking necessary corrective action will be charge on top.
For FCL bookings only:
It is Merchants responsibility to ensure that the gross cargo weight loaded into containers does not exceed the maximum payload as specified by container manufacturers and classification societies and clearly indicated on every container. In case of Pre-/On-Carriage it is Merchants responsibility that weight does comply with the valid legal and/or local limitations
As indicated in the transport plan, the port facilities, if given, are planned and therefore subject to change at the carrier's discretion.
All the local charges occurring at Peru to be paid by the merchants duly identified in the BL. These local charges are published on the website https://agenciacolumbus.com/servicios/tarifario/ together with a detailed description. Merchants acknowledge and accept these local charges when contracting our services, other charges might be applicable.
Hamburg Süd will not accept whale meat or whale products nor shark meat or shark products due to CITES and other restrictions and regulations governing International Trade of these products.
HAMBURG SUED A/S
ESPLANADEN 50, 1263, COPENHAGEN, DENMARK -
 Page 2 of 3
--- 2 ---
--- 3 ---
 Booking Number 2LIM014486 Fumigation of Cargo Transport Units (UN3359)
The carriage of Cargo Transport Units (CTU = Containers, etc.) under fumigation is covered by the IMDG Code whereby these units are classified in the Dangerous Goods List as UN3359, FUMIGATED CARGO TRANSPORT UNIT, Class 9.
Please refer to the IMDG Code section 5.5.2 Special provisions applicable to fumigated cargo transport units (UN3359), to the IMDG Code Supplement Recommendations on the safe use of pesticides in ships applicable to the fumigation of cargo transport units, and to the MSC.1/Circ.1361 Revised Recommendations on the safe use of pesticides in ships applicable to the fumigation of cargo transport units.
It is the shipper's responsibility to issue the appropriate dangerous goods declaration and to ensure that the Cargo Transport Units (CTUs) are clearly marked by the FUMIGATOR with the appropriate fumigation warning marks according to IMDG Code paragraph 5.5.2.3, stating the type and amount of the fumigant used and the date and time of fumigation. The fumigation warning marks shall be removed only when the fumigated cargo transport unit has been ventilated and unloaded,.
The shipper must ensure that the vessel's master is informed prior to the loading of the fumigated cargo transport unit on board.
We reserve the right to claim for compensation in case of non-performance with these rules.
For FCL Bookings only:
With receipt of this booking confirmation, the shipper or other cargo interested party undertakes to seal the container(s) with high-security seal(s) (meeting the specifications of ISO/PAS 17712 and any subsequent amendment or new definition thereof) immediately after stuffing is completed and before it is delivered to us and, as part of the shipping instructions, to forward the seal number together with the precise contents of the container to the carrier.
We reserve the right to claim for compensation in case of non-performance.
  Remarks
15-AUG-2022 21:16
Terms and Conditions
NI-2284093 / P43881 TERMINAL: RANSA PRODUCT COFFEE CONDITION: FCL/FCL / HS CODE 0901.11 IN BULK //FREIGHT PAYABLE BY ROTHFOS CORPORATION, NEW YORK SEA WAY BILL // AS PER AGREEMENT
AMS filing information (relevant for NVOCCs only):
Last Non-US Port called: MANZANILLO PA (ETD: 20-10-2022)
First US Port Called: PORT EVERGLADES US (ETA: 24-10-2022) ***Ports and dates are subject to change at anytime***
 THIS BOOKING CONFIRMATION IS SUBJECT TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF OUR BILL OF LADING OBTAINABLE FROM THE CARRIER OR THE CARRIERS WEBSITE AT: https://www.hamburgsud-line.com/liner/de/liner_services/terms_and_conditions.html
This booking confirmation is subject to compliance with UN, EU and US sanction laws. By proceeding, shipper represents that this booking in no way involves, nor shall it involve, in either context directly or indirectly, in any way any entity or person subject to Sanctions. Shipper further represents that the cargo subject of this booking will not be imported to any country subject to comprehensive sanctions following tendering by carrier of the subject cargo at port of discharge or the place of delivery, whichever is applicable. If any entity or person involved in this booking is an entity or person subject to Sanctions, the shipment will be returned to origin without exception, and shipper is responsible for all cost and risk for such return. Shipper agrees that Carrier may withhold release of cargo pending investigation to determine if the booking is in violation of Sanctions.
Freight & charges prepaid are due at the time of vessel’s departure and will be subject to a Late Payment Fee of 10% in case they remain unpaid after 10 days.
  HAMBURG SUED A/S
ESPLANADEN 50, 1263, COPENHAGEN, DENMARK -
Page 3 of 3
--- 3 ---
